https://www.mcrel.org/terms-of-use-privacy-policy/

Terms of Use & Privacy Policy
This site and its original content, features, and functionality are owned by McREL International and are protected by international copyright, trademark, and other intellectual property laws.
Your use of the site is subject to these Terms of Use (“Terms”). McREL reserves the right to update and change the Terms from time to time without notice or acceptance by you. By using this site, you signify your irrevocable acceptance of these Terms.
This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. If you are under 13, you may not use this site.
McREL PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy is relevant only for McREL’s website(s) and does not apply to McREL’s printed publications, conferences and other events, or any other media or presentations outside of the McREL website(s). This policy applies only to information collected by McREL through a McREL website and not to information disclosed, obtained or used by McREL through other means. McREL may provide links to unaffiliated websites for which this privacy policy does not apply. If you are unsure whether a website is controlled, affiliated, or managed by McREL, we recommend that you review the privacy policy at each linked website to determine how that site treats your personal information.
McREL may change this privacy policy from time to time. The revised policy will be posted on the McREL website.  Please check this page periodically for changes.
Personal Information:
In order to access some content on the website and to register to receive McREL newsletters and resources, McREL may require website visitors to provide some or all of the following personally identifying information (PIN): your name, job title, organization, e-mail address, postal address, phone number.
In general, McREL uses your information to administer the McREL websites and to provide information and services you request.
Aggregate information may also be used to perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analysis of website visitors to help diagnose problems with our services and our websites. In addition, McREL may share aggregate information with third parties such as business partners.
McREL may use the information collected in order to inform you of other McREL products or services, and those from our business partners.
McREL may disclose and use the information collected where required to do so by law, or where McREL, in good faith, believes the use or disclosure of the information collected is necessary to (1) comply with the law or legal processes; (2) protect and defend McREL rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of any McREL website; or to (4) protect the personal safety or property of users or the public. McREL may also use the information collected when, in its sole discretion, it believes necessary or appropriate in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of McREL’s assets.
Feedback, Commentary, Surveys, Message Boards, Chat Rooms, Blogs:
Some chat room and message board and blog forums may require registration and the sharing of PIN. Any information disclosed in chat rooms, forums, message boards, blogs and/or other interactive website groups becomes public information. Such information is not subject to this policy. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in public forums. McREL does not send spam, however, other parties may view or mine your email address or other PIN from public forums and send spam. Therefore, you should consider taking steps to prevent spam from being sent to the email address you provide in such interactive website forums.
Computer Identifying Information:
The information personal to your computer and your computer use automatically is referred to as computer identifying information (CIN). The CIN gathered by McREL generally includes cookies, specific website page requests, the domain name (e.g., www.mcrel.org) and Internet Service Provider (e.g., Comcast, American Online, NetZero) from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol address of your computer, the browser software (e.g., Internet Explorer or Netscape), and operating system (e.g., Windows XP, 2000, MacOS) you are using, your geographic location, the time and date you accessed the site, and the Internet address you visited prior to visiting the site.
USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED
In general, McREL uses your information to administer the McREL websites and to provide information and services you request.
Aggregate information may also be used to perform statistical, demographic and marketing analysis of website visitors to help diagnose problems with our services and our websites. In addition, McREL may share aggregate information with third parties such as advertisers and business partners.
YOUR INFORMATION, YOUR CHOICE
If you do not wish to share your information, you always have the option to not provide the information or use the McREL service that requires it.
McREL Opt-Out: If, at any time, you do not want to receive information about offers and new products and features from McREL, simply follow the unsubscribe options at the bottom of the email(s), or e-mail us at website@mcrel.org, or write to us at the address below. If you choose to opt-out via email, please put “McREL OPT-OUT” in the subject line.
Mailing address for Opt-Out requests or change requests:
McREL International
Attn: Website Coordinator
4601 DTC Blvd., Suite 500
Denver Colorado 80237
Please include your name and the address to which you would like us to respond, and identify the nature of your request in detail.
SECURITY
McREL uses procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to the information collected on the McREL websites. Although such protective measures have been put in place, McREL cannot ensure that the information collected will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Under California law, California residents may request certain information regarding McREL’s disclosure of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please e-mail us at website@mcrel.org or write to us at:
McREL International
Attn: Website Coordinator
4601 DTC Blvd., Suite 500
Denver, Colorado 80237
Please include your name and the address to which you would like us to respond, and identify the nature of your request in detail.
CHANGES AND QUESTIONS
McREL may change this privacy policy from time to time. The revised policy will be posted on the McREL website. Please check this page periodically for changes.
If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or practices, please contact the privacy coordinator using the contact information provided below.
McREL International
Attn: Website Coordinator
4601 DTC Blvd., Suite 500
Denver, Colorado 80237
website@mcrel.org
MODIFICATIONS TO SITE
McREL reserves the right to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, this site (or any part thereof) with or without notice at any time. You agree that McREL shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension, or discontinuance of this site.
McREL’S PROPRIETARY RIGHTS
You acknowledge and agree that this site and any necessary software used in connection with this site (“Software”) contains proprietary and confidential information that is protected by applicable intellectual property and other laws. Except as expressly authorized by McREL, you agree not to modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute or create derivative works based on this site or the Software, in whole or in part.
McREL does not want to receive confidential or proprietary information from you through this site or by email. Unless otherwise agreed in writing by an authorized McREL representative, any material, information or idea you transmit to McREL by any means may be disseminated or used by McREL or its affiliates without compensation or liability to you for any purpose whatsoever, including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing, and marketing products. However, this provision does not apply to personal information that is subject to our Privacy Policy.
DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES
You expressly understand and agree that:
(a) your use of the site is at your sole risk. The site is provided on an “as is” and “as available” basis. McREL expressly disclaims all warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement.
(b) McREL is not responsible for any damage, loss of data, customer information, vendor data or revenue, or other harm to business arising out of delays, misdelivery or nondelivery of information, restriction or loss of access, bugs or other errors, unauthorized use due to your sharing of access to the site, or other interaction with the site. McREL does not warrant that (i) the site will meet your specific requirements, or (ii) that access to the site will be uninterrupted, timely, secure, or error-free, or (iii) that the results that may be obtained from the use of the site will be accurate or reliable, or (iv) that the quality of any products, services, information, or other material purchased or obtained by you through the site will meet your expectations, or (v) that any errors in the software will be corrected.
(c) any material downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of the site is done at your own discretion and risk and you will be solely responsible for any damage to your computer system or loss of data that results from the download of any such material.
(d) no advice or information, whether oral or written, obtained through or from the site shall create any warranty not expressly stated in the terms.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
You expressly understand and agree that McREL shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or exemplary damages, including, but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, use, or data or other intangible losses (even if McREL has been advised of the possibility of such damages) resulting from: (i) the use of or the inability to use the site; (ii) unauthorized access to or alteration of your transmissions, content or data; (iii) statements or conduct of any third party on the site; or (iv) any other matter relating to the site.
EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS
Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain warranties or the limitation or exclusion of liability for incidental or consequential damages. Accordingly, some of the above limitations may not apply to you.
DIGITAL MILLENNIUM COPYRIGHT ACT
If you believe in good faith that any Content appearing on this site infringes your copyright, you may send McREL a notice that the infringing content should be removed or access to it blocked. The notice must include the following information, as required by The Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998, (“DMCA”) 17 U.S.C. Sec. 512:
A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed (or if multiple copyrighted works located on this site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works);
Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity, and information reasonably sufficient to allow McREL to locate the material;
The name, address, telephone number and email address (if available) of the complaining party;
A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law; and
A statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
Also, be aware that there may be penalties for false claims under the DMCA.
McREL’s copyright agent may be reached at:
McREL International
Attn: Copyright
4601 DTC Blvd., Suite 500
Denver COLORADO 80237
Telephone:  303.337.0990
website@mcrel.org
GOVERNMENT RESTRICTED RIGHTS
The materials on this site are provided with “RESTRICTED RIGHTS.” Use, duplication or disclosure by the U.S. Government is subject to restrictions as set forth in applicable laws and regulations. Use of the materials by the U.S. Government constitutes acknowledgment of McREL’s proprietary rights in them.
GENERAL
Notices to you may be made via either email or regular mail. The site may also provide notices of changes to the Terms or other matters by displaying notices or links to notices to you generally on this site. The Terms and the relationship between you and McREL shall be governed by the laws of the State of Colorado without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You and McREL agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located within Denver, Colorado. The failure of McREL to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Terms shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. The Terms constitute the entire agreement between you and McREL and govern your use of this site, superseding any prior agreements between you and McREL (including, but not limited to, any prior versions of the Terms). You also may be subject to additional terms and conditions that may apply when you use affiliate or other McREL services, third-party content or third-party software. If any provision of the Terms or incorporated documents are found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties’ intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of the Terms remain in full force and effect. You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of this site or the Terms must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred. The section titles in the Terms are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect.
McREL CATALOG
ABOUT McREL
Who We Are—McREL Staff
News
Careers
Contact
SERVICES
McREL Catalog
© 2020 McREL International.
|
Terms of Use & Privacy Policy
